(Penny:)You really
didn't have to...
(Penny:)Whoa!
(Penny:)That is anatomic.
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Amy:)The veins are gummy worms.
(Bernadette:)Oh, look,
(Bernadette:)Jewish and gentile.
(Amy:)I had extra dough.
(phone chimes)
(Penny(reading text):)Oh, that's Leonard.
(Penny(reading text):)He said they're about
to cross the border.
(Bernadette:)I hope the boys don't get
too crazy in Mexico.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, right.
Lock up your daughters
(Penny:)or Sheldon might
lecture them
(Penny:)about the North American
Free Trade Agreement.
(Amy:)Boy, that was
a long night for me.
(Sheldon:)Uh-oh.
(Sheldon:)According to this
Mexican Customs Web site,
(Sheldon:)visitors may not bring
more than five laser discs,
(Sheldon:)20 compact discs
(Sheldon:)or 12 VHS tapes.
(Raj:)We don't have
any of those.
(Sheldon:)How can you be sure?
(Sheldon:)VHS was king
when Feynman drove this van.